let's look at the answer for our way
prediction quiz we can use way
prediction in any cache that has more
than one block in a set a direct mapped
cache has only one block in a set so we
cannot use way prediction basically a
direct mapped cache already knows which
one block to access without having to
guess in any set associative or fully
associative cache we can benefit from a
prediction for example in a 2-way
set-associative cache we can guess which
one of the two is more likely to have
the block in an 8 way set associative
cache we are guessing which one of the
eight and in a fully associative cache
we are guessing which block in the whole
cache is the most likely to have the
block so the correct answer is that
these should be selected and this one
should not